Gabriel B. Casella

http://gbc921.github.io

gabrielbcasella@gmail.com

INTRODUCTION I work as a consultant on the APM market, helping computer systems to work faster, better and reliable as possible. In order to achieve this, the end user experience should always be the key.

> To achieve this I have experience in the areas of infrastructure, networking, programming and automation.

> In addition, I am member of the UTFPR open-source group and the abnTEX2 latex template project.

RECENT PROFESSIONAL **EXPERIENCES**

Dynatrace January 2015

APM Consultant

Dynatrace APM Training – 5 months

mstech April 2014 - December 2014

Python programmer

- Python2 programmer to Linux and Windows environments;
- Updated deb packages to comply with standard practices;
- Installed and managed VMs of Redmine, Gerrit, Nexus, OpenID;
- Created standard class in LATEX 2_{ε} to document new and existing projects.

UTFPR March 2011 - December 2011

Undergraduate Researcher

• Worked with a desktop grid distributed system, written in Java, focused on the balance of price integration among the cooperatives, the client and the server;

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

2010 - 2014

UTFPR - Federal Technological University of Paraná

Ponta Grossa, PR, Brazil

Major: Computer Science

CAPES-CsF exchange student program:

Bachelor of Science January 2012 - December 2012

Western Michigan University Kalamazoo, MI, USA

Major: Computer Science

Undergraduated Technical Course 2007 - 2009

Technical Industrial College - CTI, UNESP Bauru, SP, Brazil

Major: Computer Technician

COMPUTER **SKILLS**

Shell Script, Vim, $\prescript{LTEX}\ 2_{\prescript{\mathcal E}}$, git, C++, C#, Java, Python 2, SQL, HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3, Tornado, LibreOffice, Virtualbox, ns-3, CSMA/CA, basic Agile Programming methodology and Scrum.